<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[The Right to Retribution]]>
		</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[Set in Austin Texas, The Right to Retribution is a novel that delves into the complexities of justice, morality, and the human capacity for forgiveness. Set against the backdrop of the controversial and fictional 30th Amendment to the United States Constitution, which allows citizens the right to lawfully request the termination of one individual's life, the story follows Emily Jernigan, a high school English teacher in Austin, Texas, whose moral convictions are put to the ultimate test. Her world is shattered when Hannah is killed, and she faces a moral and ethical dilemma when David is acquitted. Emily's decision to invoke the amendment propels her into uncharted waters, testing her values and exposing the rifts in her family and community. Emily is supported by her husband, Wade, who offers steadfast love, her best friend, Claire Adams, a lawyer who opposes Emily's choice but remains loyally by her side, and her father, Joe Rawlings, a man of integrity who fears for his daughter's soul.<br/><br/>

As Emily navigates the legal and emotional complexities of her decision, she is confronted by a groundswell of opposition, including smear campaigns and societal ostracism. David Rutledge's own machinations to paint Emily as the villain exacerbate her turmoil. She also must contend with revelations of a flawed approval process for her application to invoke the amendment, leading to a crisis of conscience. Throughout her journey, Emily is forced to question the very foundations of justice and retaliation, and her own capacity for forgiveness. This is mirrored in her interactions with David, who reveals his own trauma and suffering, challenging Emily's views on what constitutes just punishment. <br/><br/><a href="https://zachleach.substack.com?utm_medium=podcast">zachleach.substack.com</a>]]>
		</description>
		<link>https://zachleach.substack.com/podcast</link>
		<generator>Substack</generator>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:27:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/zleach/rtr/main/podcast-final.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
		<author>
			<![CDATA[Zachary Leach]]>
		</author>
		<copyright>
			<![CDATA[Zach Leach]]>
		</copyright>
		<language>
			<![CDATA[en]]>
		</language>
		<webMaster>
			<![CDATA[zachleach@substack.com]]>
		</webMaster>
		<itunes:new-feed-url>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/zleach/rtr/main/podcast-final.xml</itunes:new-feed-url>
		<itunes:author>Zachary Leach</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Short stories from a forgotten and faded world.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
		<itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>Zachary Leach</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>zachleach@substack.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:category text="Fiction">
			<itunes:category text="Drama"/></itunes:category>
		<itunes:category text="Arts">
			<itunes:category text="Books"/></itunes:category>
		<itunes:image href="https://cdn.gamma.app/zc87vhr30n8uf3n/0cf7d19c27024ad59cd414c04af0c7d0/original/Black-and-White-Text-Law-Day-Social-Media-Graphic.png"/>

    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 1</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>1</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the heart of Texas, where the echoes of frontier justice still resonate beneath the vast, azure sky, Emily Jernigan grapples with a power that is as formidable as it is unsettling—the newly sanctified American right to exact legally sanctioned retribution. As an English teacher, she bears the burden of educating youth on the stark ramifications of such a law, while in the privacy of her own life, she is ensnared in the labyrinth of a moral quandary, where the lines of vengeance and justice blur. Through a landscape punctuated by the unyielding thrum of high school academia, the intimacy of marriage, and the spectral silence of a childhood wrought with memories, Emily navigates a path strewn with the gravitas of choice, the weight of untold secrets, and the plaintive yearning for a peace that seems as elusive as the whispering prairie winds.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%201.mp3" length="16489382" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%201.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:17:10</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 2</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>2</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In Chapter 2 of "Right to Retribution," the dichotomy of life's gentle moments against the backdrop of potential darkness unfolds through Emily Jernigan's seemingly unremarkable yet profound interactions. As she guides her hands through the earth, planting seeds in both the physical and metaphorical sense, she is confronted by the gratitude of a student whose life she's touched and a father's awkward acknowledgment of the role she's played in his daughter's salvation. Yet beneath these tender layers of community and growth lies a disquieting crossroad that tugs at Emily's conscience, a lurking decision that could shift her from nurturer to avenger, and stake her claim in an unseen, morally fraught battleground. With every gesture of kindness, her inner turmoil sharpens, teetering on the edge of a precipice that could redefine her very essence.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%202.mp3" length="6990016" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%202.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:16</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 3</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>3</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In a slow unfurling of routine amidst the relentless Texas heat, Emily's seemingly mundane morning throes with undiscovered currents when a voice from the past resurfaces with unexpected intentions. As she grapples with the delicate balancing act between her vocation as a nurturer of young minds and the hollow quest for retribution that nightfall brings, the sudden interest from Noah, a forgotten college acquaintance, threatens to breach the protective walls she has meticulously constructed around her life. In this chapter of "Right to Retribution," the juxtaposition of a community's accolade against the private struggle with unresolved grief and the flickering possibility of old flames reignited raises questions about the true cost of recognition and the shadows it can cast upon the soul.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%203.mp3" length="9347303" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%203.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:44</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 4</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>4</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the quiet mundanity of her home, Emily grapples with the profound and disquieting offer of sanctioned retribution for her sister's untimely fate, as a voice on the other end of a phone call—a government official named James—guides her through the cold, calculated steps of legal vengeance. Each word from James weighs heavily in the air, like a stone in water, rippling through Emily’s moral landscape, challenging her conception of justice and her thirst for closure. His voice, tinged with a sorrowful understanding, paints a picture of a society that walks the razor's edge between righteousness and retribution, leaving Emily to balance on the precipice of a decision that is at once repellent and seductive, the power to end a life as tangible and as distant as the smooth, cold granite beneath her fingertips.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%204.mp3" length="6195042" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%204.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:27</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 5</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>5</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In a chapter tinged with poignant reflection, we delve deep into Emily's haunted past as she grapples with the tragic loss of her sister—a loss that painfully intertwines with the deceit and darkness lurking behind political ambition and a facade of charm. As Emily stands alone, peeling back layers of memory as easily as potato skins, a dormant resolve within her stirs. Shaken by the cruelty of fate and the ghosts of unspoken words, a newfound determination emerges from the shadows of grief. In the silence of her introspection, a fierce and terrifying power begins to take hold, leading Emily to a pivotal crossroads between despair and the quest for retribution.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%205.mp3" length="4506923" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%205.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:04:41</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 6</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>6</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the simmering heat of personal vendetta and legal consequence, Emily Jernigan steps through the imposing doors of the state's administrative offices to confront an unfathomable choice. Confronted by the faces of loss echoing from sidewalk shrines, and the harrowing cries of protesters denouncing her potential actions, she must navigate the paper-thin line between justice and vengeance. As she submits her application for the right to exact retribution, a chance encounter with James, a clerk bearing his own scars from the system, forces Emily to question the weight of her decision and the true cost of peace. Bound by the cold bureaucracy of a system that both empowers and revolts, Emily is left grappling with the shadows cast by an irrevocable step towards retribution—one that could bring closure or cast her deeper into the abyss of moral ambiguity.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%206.mp3" length="12130495" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%206.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:12:38</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 7</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>7</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the shadowed quiet of a restless night, Emily's battle with her demons weaves an undercurrent of tension through a seemingly mundane evening. As she grapples with the weight of a life-altering decision, her interactions with Wade oscillate between the comfort of established routines and the raw urgency of their physical connection—a fleeting escape from her inner turmoil. In the dead of night, the glow of her phone screen casts an eerie light on her face, revealing the pull of both present struggles and the digital whispers of a polarized world that waits beyond the threshold of her home. Caught in the throes of vulnerability, she reaches out into the void for a familiar voice, a testament to the timeless human need for connection amid the cacophony of life's relentless noise.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%207.mp3" length="7552592" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%207.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 8</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>8</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily confronts the tortuous path of seeking justice as her resolve deepens, bringing her friendship with Claire to a fragile crux. In the lingering warmth of an Upper Gulf Coast evening, the two women grapple with the weight of vengeance and the cost of seeking retribution under the shadow of a potentially life-altering Amendment. As the chapter unfolds, echoes of the past resonate against the present turmoil, while the nostalgia of a once-shared life is tinged with the painful reality of irreparable decisions, leaving Emily to contend with the loneliness of her crusade.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%208.mp3" length="8768010" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%208.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 9</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>9</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the veiled corners of a quiet school lounge, whispers circle around English teacher Emily Jernigan, whose personal tragedy has become the subject of hushed speculation and gossip among her colleagues. Amidst the echoes of casual prejudice and the grim shadow of an upcoming active shooter drill, Emily grapples with the weight of a decision that could shatter her life even further. As she delves into Shakespeare's study of guilt and consequence with her students, the lines between fiction and reality begin to blur, revealing the haunting parallels between Lady Macbeth's torment and her own looming retribution. With an appointment that may seal her fate and strained bonds of friendship testing her resolve, Emily stands on the precipice of an action that teeters between justice and destruction—a path from which there may be no return.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%209.mp3" length="14706367" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%209.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:15:19</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 10</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>10</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily's resolve is thoroughly tested as she undergoes a psychological evaluation with Dr. Michaels, a probing session designed to determine her fitness to invoke the state's controversial Right to Retribution. As she navigates the depths of her past, revealing layers of childhood trauma and the shadows that have followed her into adulthood, Emily confronts the intertwining of her grief and her desire for justice. With Dr. Michaels as her steady yet insistent guide, she peers into the mirror of her own psyche, searching for clarity. After the session, she is drawn into the dark echoes of shared regret online, leading her to question the true cost of vengeance. As the chapter closes, the boundaries between Emily's inner turmoil and the external world blur, leaving her at the precipice of a decision that could echo with irreversible consequences.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2010.mp3" length="11810336" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2010.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:12:18</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 11</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>11</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the warmth of a family Thanksgiving gathering at the Rawlings Ranch, Emily is jolted by a message that pulls her into a silent turmoil, overshadowing the festive reunion. As the innocent laughter of children punctuates the air, she musters the courage to reveal to her loved ones the weighty decision she's made in invoking the Right to Retribution against the man responsible for her sister's death. As the ramifications of her choice ripple through the gathering, we watch as Emily navigates the intimate and complex dance of familial solidarity, personal vendetta, and an unwavering quest for justice. A blend of heartwarming tradition and stark reality, Emily's story plumbs the depths of loss and the stark lengths one might go to seek closure.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2011.mp3" length="16755204" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2011.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:17:27</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 12</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>12</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily finds herself stranded at the end of a long day—her car failing her just when she craves the comforts of home. As her mechanic husband comes to her aid, a seemingly ordinary day takes a sharp turn when the airwaves of the auto shop carry the voice of State Representative David Rutledge—a man deeply entwined with Emily's quest for justice under the shadow of the 30th Amendment. With the announcement of a series of town hall meetings aimed at discussing the future of this controversial law, Emily realizes that her personal struggle has catapulted into the public domain, where the lines between truth and political maneuvering blur. As the chapter unfolds, the radio's conservative talk paints a chilling picture of the battle Emily will face—a battle that extends far beyond the courtroom and into the very values that Texans hold dear.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2012.mp3" length="13285731" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2012.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:13:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 13</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>13</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[A seemingly routine gathering of old friends at Perry's Steakhouse spirals into a night of unforeseen terror for Emily and her husband, Wade. Amidst the laughter and nostalgia, the dark shadow of an ongoing conflict—a battle over the controversial 30th Amendment—looms, drawing Emily and her friends into a deeply personal and political debate. After the friends stumble into a merry stupor, their lighthearted return home is jarringly upended by an act of malicious intimidation, transforming the sanctuary of their home into a chilling tableau of threat. With emotions running high and alliances tested, Emily must navigate the murky waters of fear, betrayal, and the harsh realities of standing up for justice, all while a sinister force seeks to silence her fight. The stakes are raised, and the message is clear: the truth might not be as safe as it seems.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2013.mp3" length="18363092" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2013.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:19:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 14</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>14</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In a world where personal boundaries are easily trespassed and the sanctity of home is violently disrupted, Emily finds herself grappling with the unsettling aftermath of a harrowing incident at her abode. A simple visit to her father's ranch morphs into a stark confrontation with the necessity of self-defense as she is introduced to the cold steel of protection. As the rugged Texas landscape bears silent witness, Emily must navigate the complicated weave of family ties, long-standing traditions, and the unspoken expectations of what it means to stand one's ground. Amidst memories of a wilder youth and the looming threat to her present, Emily faces the daunting challenge of embracing a power she never desired, drawing lines she isn't sure she wants to defend.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2014.mp3" length="14614002" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2014.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:15:13</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 15</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>15</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[With a tumultuous call to her estranged mother, Emily grapples with unresolved issues of neglect and accusation, laying bare the emotional toll of her sister's death. Just as she navigates this personal turmoil, a startling revelation surfaces – David Rutledge announces his candidacy for U.S. Senate, a strategic maneuver that threatens to shield him from the very justice Emily seeks. This chapter delves into the depths of family dynamics, the struggle for closure, and the murky waters of political ambition, leaving Emily to muster the strength to confront an increasingly complex and vindictive battle.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2015.mp3" length="14292175" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2015.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:14:53</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 16</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>16</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Tensions boil over into violence, leaving behind a trail of consequences and heartfelt admissions. When Emily rushes to the hospital to confront her husband Wade after a workplace altercation spirals out of control, she uncovers layers of loyalty, misguided heroism, and the raw edges of personal and political battles. They grapple with the consequences of their choices, seeking solace in the promise of a simpler, quieter moment in the future. But beneath the surface, there is an unspoken recognition of the disturbing undercurrents in their lives, hinting at deeper conflicts and the unsettling awareness that some battles may be unavoidable.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2016.mp3" length="8343785" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2016.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:08:41</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 17</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>17</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[A chilling email shatters the tranquility of Emily's seaside escape, plunging her into a vortex of uncertainty. As she grapples with a cryptic warning that her quest for justice is being deliberately sabotaged by unseen forces, the lines between ally and adversary begin to blur. With the steadfast support of Wade and the strategic mind of Claire, Emily ventures to navigate this treacherous unknown. A clandestine meeting is set against the backdrop of an unassuming diner, where answers await and the specter of betrayal casts a long shadow. Will Emily's pursuit of the elusive Right to Retribution lead to revelation or ruin? The truth teeters on a knife-edge, and every choice could be a step towards vindication or a descent into peril.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2017.mp3" length="9628174" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2017.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:10:01</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 18</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>18</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily embarks on a lone journey that seeps into the shadows of a corrupted system, her path leading to a clandestine meeting with a haunted whistleblower. Amidst the nostalgic backdrop of a Texas diner, a web of conspiracy unfurls as Emily and her stalwart friend, Claire, uncover the disturbing manipulation of a law meant for justice. What begins as a quest for retribution spirals into a chilling realization that the very foundation of Emily's fight is riddled with treachery. As the secrets of a digital underworld bleed into the reality of her crusade, a young man's remorse casts a long, dark shadow, threatening the justice Emily seeks for Hannah. When her journey back home is interrupted by an abrupt reminder of life's fragility, Emily faces a crossroads where the weight of truth and the taste of an incongruously delicious pie blend into a poignant tapestry of laughter and tears.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2018.mp3" length="19057321" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2018.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:19:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 19</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>19</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the haunting twilight of their coastal retreat, Emily and Wade's final day unfolds with an unexpected encounter that leads to an invitation to a New Year's Eve party hosted by local residents, Jeannie and Troy. As the night unravels, Emily is swept into a tumultuous sea of emotions, struggling to keep afloat amidst the memories of her sister and the dark shadow cast by David Rutledge's trial. As the countdown to midnight echoes with revelry and resolutions, Emily finds herself on a precipice, her cries lost amidst the fireworks and waves, only to be drawn back by Wade's unwavering support. A glimpse into their intertwined journey reveals a landscape of love and resilience, but also the harrowing depths of a soul yearning for retribution and a respite from its burdening past.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2019.mp3" length="17818909" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2019.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:18:33</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 20</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>20</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily grapples with the haunting specters of her past and the weighty decision to rid herself of a protective but burdensome firearm. A series of harrowing events, from the mysterious shadow at her window to a confrontation with her own capacity for darkness, propel Emily on an odyssey through the Texan night. As she navigates the murky waters between justice and retribution, the choices she faces illuminate the strength and fragility of her resolve. Will her personal quest for peace and order lead her down a path from which there can be no return, or will the moral compass she so desperately clings to guide her to safe harbor?]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2020.mp3" length="17280581" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2020.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:17:59</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 21</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>21</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the shrouded stillness of the Texan night, Emily finds herself on a path of introspection and relinquishment, guided by the wisdom of her solitary Uncle Dan. Surrendering a totem of her fears, she inherits a poignant legacy—a box filled with memories of her lost sister, Hannah. As Emily navigates the dark contours of her own vulnerabilities and the haunting legacy of love and loss left in her sister's wake, she must confront the shadows of the past to find her way back to the light of home. In a narrative where the rural Texas terrain becomes a metaphor for the vast and uncharted territories of the heart, Emily's journey is a poignant exploration of grief, resilience, and the indomitable power of family bonds.
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2021.mp3" length="14521632" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2021.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:15:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 22</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>22</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily faces the excruciating intersection of personal tribulations and professional jeopardy, as her decision to invoke a contentious legal amendment reverberates through the school corridors and into the hallowed conference rooms of the conservative school board. A moral quandary takes shape against the backdrop of her beloved classroom, where literature's mirroring of life's darkest illusions becomes a stark reality. As the community's whispers turn into a roar calling for her undoing, Emily must navigate the precarious battle lines drawn between her quest for justice and the societal forces arrayed against her. With her career hanging by a thread, she finds a flicker of hope in a new stratagem, one that might just tip the scales in a game where the stakes are higher than ever before.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2022.mp3" length="19797110" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2022.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:20:37</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 23</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>23</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[The justice takes a serendipitous turn when she reconnects with Noah, an old college acquaintance who has since become an esteemed political reporter. As a storm rages outside, the two seek refuge in a cozy coffee shop, where a casual catch-up veers into a clandestine exchange of information and confessions. With the revelation of a potential conspiracy that could undermine her cause, Emily finds herself entangled in a web of political intrigue, her personal strife compounded by the resurfacing of unresolved emotions. As the rain subsides, so too do the barriers of the past, and Emily leaves armed with new allies and secrets that draw her deeper into the shadows of retribution and the murky waters of state politics.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2023.mp3" length="17408477" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2023.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:18:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 24</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>24</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[A seemingly routine birthday celebration at a Texas bar becomes a backdrop for the measured dance of camaraderie and conspiracy. As Emily navigates the boisterous tides of laughter and beer-soaked bravado, the deeper undercurrents of her precarious situation churn ominously beneath the surface. With her friend Claire by her side, they steal moments of escape and strategy in the chill of the night. But even as shadows lengthen with the weight of impending revelations and the risks of digging too deep, the steady warmth of Wade's presence offers a poignant reminder that, amidst life's complexities, love endures as a guiding beacon. The stakes mount, pulling readers further into a web where loyalty, justice, and the personal costs of a fight for truth become ominously entangled.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2024.mp3" length="21156315" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2024.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:22:02</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 25</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>25</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the heart of the Texan winter, a decision made in the name of justice sends ripples through the Rawlings family, challenging the bonds of blood and belief. As Emily stands before the dying embers of family unity, she must confront the legacy of loss and the shadow of vengeance that looms over the ranch. In choosing a path of forgiveness over retribution, she defies not only her town's thirst for punishment but also the very tenets that have shaped her steadfast father, Joe Rawlings. The cold chill of the outside world mirrors the icy divide that threatens to sever the ties that bind, leaving readers to wonder if the principles of the past can reconcile with the hope for a healing future.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2025.mp3" length="18642709" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2025.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:19:25</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 26</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>26</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily grapples with the haunting shadows of her past as she seeks to uncover the identity of the enigmatic Marcus, the potential whistleblower who holds the key to a political scandal that could shake the very foundations of her community. As she delves into the depths of her memories and sifts through old yearbooks, the lines between her role as an educator and her moral compass blur, pushing her into a precarious dance with professional boundaries and personal convictions. With each page turn and each recollection, Emily finds herself inching closer to the truth, the echoes of a shared history with Marcus guiding her towards an uncertain confrontation with forces larger than herself. Will the whispers of the past lead her to salvation or to deeper peril? The stakes have never been higher as Emily stands at the precipice, ready to leap into the flood that could sweep her towards destiny or demise.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2026.mp3" length="14698849" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2026.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:15:18</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 27</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>27</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In a chapter seeped in secrets and silent battles, Emily embarks on a journey that takes her into the heart of her former student's troubled world. As the shadows of the 30th Amendment loom ominously over the lives it touches, she grapples with a reality where the lines are blurred between the political and personal. Amidst heartfelt reunions and cryptic exchanges, a small flash drive becomes the fulcrum on which the scales of justice might tip. But as the day's events unfold into an evening of unexpected alliances and intimate revelations, Emily and those she holds dear find themselves ensnared in a web of intrigue that promises to shake the very foundations of their reality.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2027.mp3" length="25101421" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2027.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:26:08</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 28</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>28</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Jolted awake by an early call, Emily sets her destiny on a collision course with the dark underbelly of justice and retribution—a termination date for David Rutledge is set. With her world reeling and a stark 48-hour ultimatum to reverse the course, she seeks refuge in the normalcy of a Sunday morning: a Pure Barre class with her friend Claire. But beneath the bustling cadence of shared workouts and caffeine-fueled conversations, a deeper turmoil stirs. Emily grapples with the weight of choices that bridge the chasm between life and death, secrets that linger in unopened boxes, and the stark reality that the past is never just a memory. As she confronts the shadows of her sister's legacy and her own apprehensions, the narrative delves into the power of friendship and the courage to face what we fear most, all while the clock ticks down on a choice that will forever alter the tapestry of lives entwined with her own.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2028.mp3" length="19694287" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2028.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:20:30</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 29</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>29</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[Emily embarks on an emotionally charged journey through the remnants of her late sister's life, preserved within a dusty box filled with memories and secrets. As she unveils trinkets and mementos of Hannah's existence—ranging from childhood keepsakes to the more troubling artifacts of her adulthood—Emily is confronted with an unexpected letter that will challenge her understanding of forgiveness and the indelible bonds of sisterhood. In this solemn exploration of the personal items left behind, Emily is drawn closer to the mysteries that enshroud her sister's untimely demise, uncovering a narrative that is as heart-rending as it is telling, leading her to reckon with a past fraught with love, loss, and the relentless pursuit of truth.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2029.mp3" length="13894281" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2029.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:14:28</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 30</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>30</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[A storm brews not only in the sky but in the hearts of our characters as Emily Rawlings confronts a tempest of emotion. Central Texas’ unpredictable wrath tears across the landscape, uprooting more than just trees - it rips through the very foundations of Emily's past. As the relentless tornado spares her father but claims the family home, questions swirl like the unforgiving winds: what remnants of her history can Emily salvage amidst the debris of nostalgia and the stark reality of loss? The Rawlings Ranch, a bastion of memories and a symbol of enduring legacy, lies in ruins, leaving Emily and Wade to navigate the aftermath as they cling to each other amidst the whispers of dawn and the unspoken fears of what daylight will reveal.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2030.mp3" length="12752417" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2030.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:13:16</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 31</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>31</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the aftermath of a devastating tornado that has stripped Emily of her childhood home and legacy, the Rawlings Ranch lies in ruin. As the community rallies to piece together the fragments of what once was, a shadow from Emily's tumultuous past re-emerges, weaving a new thread of tension into the fabric of the day's sorrow. David Rutledge, the man tried for her sister's murder, descends upon the disaster under the guise of political goodwill, igniting a firestorm of unresolved anger and setting the stage for an unexpected confrontation. With her father and the remnants of her once unshakable foundation surrounding her, Emily must navigate the complexity of loss, politics, and the pursuit of a justice that feels increasingly elusive.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2031.mp3" length="22443205" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2031.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:23:22</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 32</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>32</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[A collision of past and present unfolds amidst the wreckage of a family tragedy, where the sorrow-shrouded landscape of rural Texas serves as the backdrop for a momentous confrontation. The raw edges of grief and vengeance blur as the story dives into the depths of shared guilt, unspoken truths, and the complex tapestry of human emotion that binds together the most unlikely of souls. In a charged and poignant exchange, the characters grapple with the heavy chains of their history, and the narrative explores whether the power of forgiveness can truly mend the fractures of a splintered heart. This chapter is a stirring testament to the enduring struggle for peace in the shadow of irrevocable loss, leaving readers to ponder whether reconciliation can ever rise from the ashes of betrayal.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2032.mp3" length="13707453" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2032.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:14:16</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <itunes:title>Chapter 33</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episode>33</itunes:episode>
      <description><![CDATA[In the climactic conclusion of "Right to Retribution," Emily is enveloped in a tapestry of reconciliation and newfound understanding. In the fading light, decisions weigh heavily as Emily is pulled back to the emotional crucible of her past, seeking solace among the silent sentinels of memory in a poignant return to her sister's grave. As the redolent Texas dusk embraces her, a silent figure emerges, embodying both the sorrow and love of years gone by. Here, amid the whisper of winds and the stoic comfort of headstones, the deepest scars of abandonment and the tender shoots of forgiveness intertwine, crafting a moment of vulnerability and profound connection that promises a horizon illuminated with the fragile rays of hope.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2033.mp3" length="8754638" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://github.com/zleach/rtr/raw/main/Chapter%2033.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>